{
    "subject": "resource/TextDrive",
    "predicate": "property/headquarters",
    "object": "resource/San_Francisco",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of TextDrive are located in San Francisco.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8884082436561584,
            "question": "Where is the headquarters of TextDrive located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7131205797195435,
            "question": "What is the geographical address of TextDrive's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6070130467414856,
            "question": "In what city are the offices of TextDrive situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45631304383277893,
            "question": "Where is the central command for TextDrive situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4291735887527466,
            "question": "Which city houses the main offices of TextDrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3860163688659668,
            "question": "What is the location of TextDrive's main operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.378100723028183,
            "question": "What urban area serves as the home base for TextDrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37021446228027344,
            "question": "Where are the primary operations of TextDrive based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3460347354412079,
            "question": "Where can you find the primary base of TextDrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34430065751075745,
            "question": "TextDrive's main office is in which city?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of TextDrive are located in San Francisco.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6729_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find the primary base of TextDrive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6729_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are the primary operations of TextDrive based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6729_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What urban area serves as the home base for TextDrive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6729_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6729_40.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Joyent, which was acquired by Samsung in 2016, was part of TextDrive and worked on projects out of Marin County. There is no mention of TextDrive's headquarters being located in San Francisco.  "
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the text states that Joyent, which is part of TextDrive, has a hosting company run by and for people who love publishing on the web out of Marin County (not San Francisco)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention that the headquarters of TextDrive are located in San Francisco. Instead, some documents discuss companies moving from the San Francisco Bay Area, but there is no specific information about the location of TextDrive's headquarters."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "TextDrive was acquired by Joyent, which is not located in San Francisco but in Marin County.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text mentions Joyent being purchased by Samsung in 2016, and that Joyent is part of TextDrive. It also states that Joyent was bootstrapped through crowdfunding with customers investing in exchange for free hosting, a model not typically associated with large companies headquartered in San Francisco.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because TextDrive is stated to be \"run by and for people who love publishing on the web out of Marin County\", which suggests that its headquarters are not in San Francisco, but rather in Marin County.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions that Joyent, which is part of TextDrive, developed a service due to the needs of its team members and that they are relocating their headquarters from the San Francisco Bay Area to Texas. This indicates that while TextDrive may have had its headquarters in San Francisco at some point, it has since relocated them.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}